{
    "answerPools": [
        {
            "id":0,
            "pool": [
                "a",
                "i",
                "u",
                "e",
                "o"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id":1,
            "pool": [
                "あ",
                "い",
                "う",
                "え",
                "お"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "questionPools":[
        {
            "id":0,
            "answerPoolId":0,
            "pool":[
                {
                    "question":"あ",
                    "answer":"a"
                },
                {
                    "question":"い",
                    "answer":"i"
                },
                {
                    "question":"う",
                    "answer":"u"
                },
                {
                    "question":"え",
                    "answer":"e"
                },
                {
                    "question":"お",
                    "answer":"o"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id":1,
            "answerPoolId":1,
            "pool":[
                {
                    "question":"a",
                    "answer":"あ"
                },
                {
                    "question":"i",
                    "answer":"い"
                },
                {
                    "question":"u",
                    "answer":"う"
                },
                {
                    "question":"e",
                    "answer":"え"
                },
                {
                    "question":"o",
                    "answer":"お"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}